[theme music playing]
[laughs]
-[goon] Lily Cruz!
-[gunfire]
[Lily] What now?! Huh?
Go ahead and have fun watching!
Because once I get out of here,
along with my mother,
I'll show you the meaning of fear!
-[glass shatters]
-[screams]
[Helena] If you hadn't stopped me,
Lily Cruz would've bitten the dust by now!
[Jepoy] Where are Lily and Auntie Camia?
[Arnaldo] I think I know where Lily is.
All I know is they were brought here.
We better look for them. They should
be around here somewhere.
[Damian] Raul, are you sure you're ready
to go against the Ardientes?
-[Raul] I'm willing to do it for my son.
-[Julio] What's this?
[Helena] That's impossible.
Damian is dead.
I saw Diego kill Damian myself.
[Emilia] What the hell is
Jaguar doing there?
[Julio] How many lives does that
damn Cruz family have?!
[Camia] Raul, why are you doing this?
[Raul] Camia, let me make up
for everything I've done.
[Emilia] Where are you two?
[Helena] Emilia.
Your right, behind the crates.
Come on out of there!
-One! Two! Three!
-[gunshots]
[Raul grunts]
[Emilia] Let go, Jaguar! You traitor!
-[Emilia grunting]
-[gunshot]
[Emilia sobbing]
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
I'm sorry, baby girl.
But your husband had it coming.
He played a very dangerous game,
and that's the price he had to pay.
Don't worry. You'll always have me.
[somber music continues]
[squealing]
[groaning] Emilia.
[Emilia sobbing]
[Emilia wailing] No!
-[crying] Raul!
-[Raul shushes]
[shushes]
Emilia. Emilia.
Forgive me.
[struggling] Forgive me if I was…
never a good husband to you.
-Emilia…
-[sobbing]
I'm sorry I hurt you so much.
I did love you. I really did.
But I guess we just weren't meant to be.
[Raul breathes raggedly]
[somber music playing]
Raul. Raul. Please.
Please, no, no. Don't. Don't.
-[Emilia crying]
-[Raul shushes]
Emilia. Emilia. Emilia.
[somber music continues]
I'm begging you… stop this.
Please… leave this all behind
before it's too late.
-Emilia…
-[crying]
[breathes raggedly]
[Emilia crying]
-[Raul breathes raggedly]
-[crying]
No. No.
[Emilia crying] No. No. No.
[Emilia] No. No!
[somber music playing]
[squealing]
[screaming]
[wailing] Raul.
[wailing]
[screaming]
[sobbing]
Raul! Raul.
No, please.
Raul.
[somber music continues]
-Huh?
-Is there something about tonight?
-What are you talking about?
-This is how we met.
I want you back.
I want things back the way they were.
Emilia, I love you so much.
I would worship you.
You know, Emilia,
when I told you
I would change, I meant it.
Emilia, I'd love to marry you again.
Yes! Yes! I'll marry you again.
Over and over.
Raul!
[sobbing]
[Emilia] Jaguar saved my life.
So why would he kill me right away?
Jaguar's quite the sweet talker, no?
Just like Raul?
[Jaguar] I want my love to be
the one to help set you free.
[Emilia] Wow, Jaguar.
What if I fall for you and
you aren't ready?
I can't believe this.
Did that just really happen?
Thank you, Jaguar!
I can't believe this! I am finally free!
[Jaguar] As long as I'm here,
no one can hurt you.
You know, I've never felt
so loved in my life.
You're the only one
who made me feel this way.
Thank you.
[crying]
Do you love me?
Mm-hm.
I don't think I can feel it, Emilia.
I love you.
[somber music playing]
[Emilia] Raul!
[Emilia crying]
I'm sorry, Raul.
I love you, but this won't end here!
I'm going to kill Lily Cruz
and Camia Cruz!
Emilia.
Emilia, stop this before it's too late.
-Emilia.
-No.
[Raul groaning]
I'll kill you both,
Lily Cruz and Camia Cruz!
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Have you found them?
[goon 2] Not yet.
Where could they be hiding?
[action music playing]
This way. Let's rest here.
Damian.
[Damian groans]
Damian, Raul is the other Jaguar?
Yeah, I gave Raul that mask
when I was in prison.
He used it to get his revenge
on the Ardientes.
Raul ruined my family.
Why did he help me?
To repent for all his sins against us?
After everything he did to us…
does he think it'd be that easy?
[somber piano music playing]
You don't owe him your forgiveness.
But try to give a chance to the
people who want to change…
so you can be free from all
the pain you're carrying.
Let's stay here for now.
[action music playing]
-Sir.
-Yes?
Lily Cruz got away.
[goon 1] And we got attacked by Jaguar.
Go on, clean that up.
Move!
[action music playing]
[Lily] You were the one
guarding my mother.
[tense music playing]
[metal clanking]
Arnaldo, I've searched the whole place,
but they aren't here.
Do you think I'm stupid? Where are they?
Hold on, I don't know.
They might've escaped,
or maybe they were moved.
-You bastard.
-I mean, it's possible.
Are you playing games with me?!
No, don't point your gun at me. I'm not--
Do you think I'm stupid?
You're stalling or something!
Where are they?!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm trying to help you, Jepoy.
Your family kidnapped them.
Why should I trust you?
They might be my family,
but you're my friends.
I won't let any one of you
get harmed, especially not Lily.
You should know that by now.
Give me one good reason
not to blow your brains out.
[exhales sharply]
[tense music playing]
I'm done trying to convince you.
If you want to shoot me, then do it.
But I'm still going to try and find Lily.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Whatever it takes.
[tense music continues]
[action music playing]
Ow.
[groans]
[grunts]
Now where is that she-devil?
[groans]
Helena.
[groaning]
You do not do this to Julio Ardiente.
You are pissing me off.
[tense music playing]
[groans]
Ow.
Oh my.
Poor stupid fool, Raul.
My! I'm so sorry.
Did you know that I did everything I could
to make you an Ardiente
because that's what
I promised your father?
But I'm sorry.
Maybe your life
was meant to end like this.
Rest in peace, Raul.
[clicks tongue]
You're so dumb.
That's what you get.
You should be proud of your daughter.
Because Emilia herself shot Raul.
[tense music playing]
Wait a minute.
Let me get this clear.
Emilia shot Raul?
[laughing]
How poetic can things get?
Can you imagine?
The first man that Emilia
ever fell in love with
is the very same man
she's killed with her own bare hands.
Poetic, isn't it?
How many times did he make
a fool out of Emilia?
That's why I'm wondering,
why did it take her so long
to finally end him?
Because she didn't know that
she'd actually shot her husband.
-Huh?
-Yes. Baby girl did not know…
that she shot Raul.
Because when she shot him,
he was wearing the Jaguar's mask.
[Helena chuckles] Yes, Julio.
Your "good-for-nothing" son-in-law…
is the fake Jaguar
that gave you so much trouble.
Ha!
Are you surprised, huh?
That traitor was right
under your nose the whole time.
Hmm.
What would the people of Ardiente say
about their governor,
the great Julio Ardiente…
being outwitted by his good-for-nothing,
womanizing son-in-law?
Huh? [laughing]
[laughing]
My! Oh, my, Helena!
-You are gravely mistaken.
-Oh.
Raul was never a threat to me!
That's why I never wasted time on him!
I could have killed him just like that.
-Just like you.
-Aww.
I could take you out anytime I want.
You have exhausted my patience!
I'm--I'm tired of… I don't--
I don't wanna play games with you anymore.
-It's not fun anymore!
-Aww.
Let's put an end to this, huh?
Huh?
-What a big gun you have.
-[Helena chuckling]
Now, why don't you point it
right at my chest…
and shoot.
Now, call my bluff if you think it is.
Come on. How about you and me, my dear?
How about we have this date in hell?
Huh?!
Come on. Shoot me. Shoot me.
-Shoot me!
-[Helena laughing]
Not tonight, Julio, my dear.
Girls.
Wha-- What's--
[Helena laughing]
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
Take Julio with you.
And please handle him with care.
Because you know
how brittle his bones are.
-This is unfair!
-[Helena laughs]
And, make sure that none of you
disturb me in here!
Bye, Julio.
-I'll kill you for--Ow!
-Sure.
Easy, girls. I can't walk.
Like… Get off me! You…
You're worst than--
-Helpless…
-Women! You're worst than men!
Ow! [grunts] You stop pushing me!
-old man.
-Ow! Ow!
Jibber-jabber. Ugh!
[tense music playing]
[coughs]
[somber music playing]
Diego. Diego. Arnaldo.
Dad?
Dad.
You're bleeding.
-Diego.
-Can you stand?
Dad. Dad, hang in there.
I'll ask for help.
Just stay here. I'll ask for help. Dad.
[shushes]
[somber music playing]
Dad.
Son.
-Dad, I'll ask for help.
-Son. [shushes]
Listen to me.
Forgive me for all my…
all my shortcomings.
Please forgive me.
Please forgive me for failing to give you…
a good life, son.
Dad. Dad. Dad, don't talk like that.
All I want now…
is for you to help your brother.
Please help Arnaldo.
Your brother needs you.
Your brother needs you!
And…
I just want you and Lily to be happy.
-Dad, you won't die.
-Son, listen to me.
-Listen to me.
-I'll save you.
-No…
When I die, you need to be strong.
No. No.
-Be strong. Okay?
-No… No… We won't give up.
Listen to what I'm telling you.
Help your brother.
-Dad, Dad. Dad.
-I love you so much. I love…
-Dad.
-I love you so much.
I love you…
Dad. Dad. Dad. I'll save--
Dad!
Dad. Dad, keep fighting!
[ominous piano music playing]
Dad.
-Dad, keep fighting.
-[Raul's breathing stops]
[ominous music continues]
Dad.
You bastards!
All of you!
You killed everyone I love!
What more do you want?!
What more?!
[ominous music playing]
[action music playing]
-Have you found them?
-No, ma'am.
[Emilia] Make sure you bar all the gates.
They're not getting out of here alive.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Check again!
Where's the control room?
Lino, go with her.
[suspenseful music building]
Camia…
[Emilia] Damian, come out!
Where are you?
Don't make this hard for me.
[keys clicking]
Come out!
Camia!
Damian!
Stop giving me a hard time.
Because there will only be one outcome.
I'll cover your bodies in bullet holes!
[somber music playing]
I killed Raul…
because of you.
[ominous music playing]
I killed my husband…
because of you.
-[screaming]
-[gunshots]
[screams]
I killed my husband because of you!
Because until the end, my
husband still chose you over me.
He chose you, Camia.
That's why…
I'll kill you.
I'll rip you two to shreds!
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
[whispering] Damn it.
Arnaldo.
Hello, Mom.
What's wrong? Why weren't you picking up?
I killed him.
[tense music playing]
Who's dead? Who did you kill?
I killed your father.
I killed him.
Where are you? I'll head there.
I'm at Camia's warehouse.
Looking for her.
And I'm going to kill that woman.
I'm going to kill them all!
[tense music swelling]
[laughing]
There they are. [laughing]
Found you two.
-Hello.
-[goon] Yes, ma'am?
They're at the mess hall.
Bring Camia here to me
because I'm going to kill her myself.
As for Damian, I'll leave him to you.
[tense music playing]
[rock music playing]
You watch that area.
[action music playing]
[goon grunts]
[grunts]
[action music playing]
[action music continues]
I'm coming, Mom.
[ominous music playing]
-Show yourselves!
-[gunshots]
[giggling]
[laughing]
[goon] Come on!
Not coming out, huh?
[gunshots]
[laughing]
[crying]
[Damian] Don't shoot!
Stop! Stop shooting!
Camia.
[crying]
We wasted all these bullets for nothing.
Take her to Ma'am Emilia!
[tense music playing]
Bang!
-Come here.
-Let me go!
-Let go of me!
-Don't touch her!
-I said come here!
-[thuds]
-[Damian grunts]
-Damian!
-I said, come here!
[Camia] Damian!
-Come here.
-Damian!
[goon] Come here! Stop resisting!
[tense music continues]
Camia!
You bastard!
[action music playing]
[goon] Say your prayers!
-[thuds]
-[screaming]
[goon] Hey!
[action music playing]
[gunshots]
Come here!
[screaming]
[gunshots]
Mr. Damian, have you found them?
I found Camia, but Emilia's men took her.
I can't find Lily.
Diego…
your father…
[somber music playing]
[goon] Move it!
-[Camia] Let me go!
-[goon] Ma'am!
Leave the two of us alone.
We'll settle this once and for all.
None of you must interfere! Get out!
[goon] Yes, ma'am!
[tense music playing]
Try to run now,
and I'll make sure
you join my cheating husband.
Aren't you tired of committing
all these crimes, Emilia?
Actually, I'm tired of chasing
around this place.
But, you know,
just to answer your question…
Yes.
I am sick and tired of this.
I'm sick and tired of you!
Ever since you moved
into Poblacion Ardiente,
you ruined my life!
You ruined my family!
I even killed my own husband
because of you.
Your family tore mine apart, Emilia.
We were living in peace.
We didn't do anything to you,
but what did you do?
You had my husband killed,
you attempted to kill my daughter,
and you had me raped!
You're sick! I was violated!
So, go ahead! Kill me now!
But, I promise you, I'll drag
you with me to my grave!
You're going to pay for this, Emilia.
You'll pay for everything
you've done to us!
Let's end this now!
[tense music playing]
Mom.
Diego.
What a surprise to see you, Lily Cruz!
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
[squealing]
[action music playing]
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[scoffs]
Finally.
I get to kill you myself!
-Where is my mother?
-Obviously, she isn't here.
She's there!
With Emilia.
You're all despicable.
Yes, we really are!
And Emilia wouldn't think twice
about killing your mother!
If she was able to kill her own husband,
how much more so your mother…
who happens to be the bane
of her existence?!
[gunshot]
[glass shattering]
[Helena screams]
[yelps]
Go on!
Well?!
Can you still fight, Mama Hel?
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
[groans]
I can't wait to shoot!
I can't wait to kill all you Ardientes!
And your stupid daughter
may have my mother.
But I have her twisted mother!
So, if your daughter
does something to my mother,
you, Helena,
will be the first one
I'll send to the grave!
[tense music playing]
I won't hold back any longer!
Right now, I'm ready to kill you.
[action music playing]
Go on!
Before this night is over,
I'll have my revenge on you
and your daughter!
I'll kill you both and bury you together!
Don't be so sure, Emilia.
No matter how many times
you try to bury us,
we'll always come back to haunt you!
Yes, you're right.
But, this time,
I'll fill both of your bodies with bullets
before I bury you together!
[tense music playing]
Oh, by the way…
I've been wanting
to do this for a long time now.
[Camia grunting]
Don't you dare!
[action music playing]
Huh?
You know, I should've killed you ages ago!
So…
did I stress you out?
Hmm? [laughing]
Say goodbye, Camia.
Say goodbye, Camia!
Say goodbye to the cruel world, Camia!
-Come here!
-[Helena groans]
Emilia!
Lily!
[tense music playing]
[Helena groaning]
Let go of my mother!
If you kill my mother,
I'll kill yours!
And I'll make sure you'll be gone
even before the sun rises!
Let go of her!
No!
[tense music continues]
Let go of my mother first.
Let go of my mama!
You still won't give in, huh?
You won't?!
[groaning]
[action music playing]
I said let go of Mama!
Tell you what.
I'm sure you don't want your mama to die.
Right, baby girl?
I'll let go of your mother.
Let's meet.
Your mother in exchange for my mother!
Well?
Well?!
[action music continues]
Lily's safe.
Diego, we need to help Camia.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
Fine.
Where will we meet?
Don't you dare try anything, Emilia.
It should just be you and my mother.
If I see any of your men…
even just the shadow of your men…
I'll blow your
precious mother's brains out.
[cries]
[laughing]
You were the man behind the mask.
It fits you, Dad, it fits you.
[tense music playing]
This…
This somehow summarizes
your pitiful life, you know?
Imagine,
you hid behind a mask
just to be a somebody.
Just like how you hid
behind the Ardiente family name
for the longest time.
Because let's face it, without Ardiente,
there is no Raul Torillo, right?
You're worthless.
And useless.
You are nothing.
Oh, no, no, no, you're not nothing.
Your worth is less than nothing.
Why? Why?
Because you were never good at anything.
You were never a good husband to Mom.
All those years of pain
you inflicted on her.
You deserve much worse.
If only I could wake you up,
revive you,
I would kill you again.
That's how much I hate you.
What? I'm sorry?
What did you say?
Oh, no, no, is this the part
where you say you're sorry?
Well, guess what? Screw you!
Don't expect me to mourn
for you now that you're gone.
Because after all…
you…
you were never a father to me.
[tense music continues]
Goal!
Bye!
[tense music playing]
They're gone.
We have to find them.
Let's go.
-[thuds]
-[Helena groans]
Stop whining. Keep walking!
Hurry! Move it!
[groans]
Keep walking, and don't even
think of escaping!
[Emilia] Faster.
-Hurry up.
-Let go of me!
[goon] You're too slow!
Stop pushing me! Stop pushing me!
[chuckling]
Wow, you've got spunk.
But, you know too bad, that
won't save you from anything.
Actually, nothing will save you.
[chuckles] Whether you
like it or not, you will die.
Be thankful that my mama
begged me to save her.
Otherwise, you'd be dead by now.
Mom can be such a burden.
She can't even escape
from your daughter, Lily Cruz!
What kind of a daughter are you?
You'd put your own mother's life
in danger?
[chuckles] You know, Camia,
you and your daughter started all this.
Well then let me go.
What did you say?
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to do that.
Are you crazy?
You and your daughter started this.
I'll take revenge for my husband.
A life for a life!
You know, which reminds me…
[tense music playing]
I'm low on ammo.
So, call for backup,
get all our explosives,
get every dangerous weapon,
and bring them to the quarry, okay?
And call your friends too.
Because I want this night to be
an explosive night to remember.
[laughs]
You bitch! You're going to
ambush my daughter? Monster!
[laughing]
-Let me go!
-What is wrong with you?!
That is what we are known for.
The Ardientes. That is our trademark.
And the fireworks will begin as
soon as I see Lily Cruz arrive.
I just wish and pray that, um,
my mama is bulletproof.
You're a monster!
You're insane!
You're rotten to the core!
You and your family!
Let go of me!
[tense music playing]
-[Camia groans]
-[goon] Stay still!
-Hey!
-Hold her.
-Zip her mouth.
-Monster!
-Oh my…
-You're a monster, Emilia!
-Stop!
Damn you!
[Emilia] Zip it. [shushes]
Now you're quiet. I'm at peace.
[Emilia] Whoo! [laughs]
What now?
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
YOUR GRANDFATHER IS ABOUT TO
BE BURIED ALIVE.
GO TO SITIO 6 WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
HURRY. HE DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH TIME LEFT.
[engine starting]
[engine revving]
You! What are you doing?
Help us.
I just needed to send a text.
[tense music continues]
[Lily] Move.
Stay there.
[dramatic music playing]
Be quiet.
[somber music playing]
Diego?
Uncle Damian.
[somber music continues]
Diego.
[somber music playing]
[Lily crying]
You're alive.
[sighs] Thank goodness you're alive.
You're safe.
[somber music continues]
[tense music playing]
You monster.
Diego. Diego, don't. Stop.
Emilia has my mother.
And as much as I want to kill this woman,
we can't do that yet.
Emilia and I will trade hostages.
But after that,
I'll kill Red Dragon myself.
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo] Thank you
for your loyal service.
[gunshot]
[Julio] Now, where is that witch,
Helena Montoya?!
I am going to kill her.
And if she survives, I'll kill her again.
-Let my mother go!
-You let my mother go!
[Emilia] At the same time!
[Camia] Lily, it's an ambush!
Shoot them, baby girl! Shoot them!
-[gunshot]
-Mama!
-[yelps]
-[gunshots and screams]
[gunfire]
[explosion]
[theme music playing]